metasrc.com 2018-08-03

# Privacy Policy [CHALLENGER][MASTER][DIAMOND][PLATINUM][GOLD][SILVER][BRONZE][PROVISIONAL] - METAsrc - League of Legends

Thank you for visiting the METAsrc Privacy Policy. METAsrc LLC (“METAsrc”, “we”, “us”) owns and operates [www.metasrc.com](http://www.metasrc.com/). This privacy policy explains how METAsrc collects, uses, and otherwise processes information through your use of our products and services available on our website [www.metasrc.com](http://www.metasrc.com/) (“website”, “site”).

By continuing to use this website, you hereby confirm that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and acknowledge that we will process all information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please immediately discontinue use of the site.

Should you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our Data Protection Officer can be contacted at [privacy@metasrc.com](mailto:privacy@metasrc.com) (please put “Privacy” in the subject line).

WHAT IS PERSONAL DATA?

“Personal Data” is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable living individual. Different pieces of information, which collected together can lead to the identification of a particular person, also constitute personal data.

Personal data that has been rendered anonymous in such a way that the individual is not or no longer identifiable is no longer considered personal data. For data to be truly anonymized, the anonymization must be irreversible.

DATA WE COLLECT

In short, we do not store or collect personal data. The only data we collect from you is made anonymous, so it is no longer considered personal data.

This data is collected for the purpose of log files and traffic analytics through Google Analytics and requires the use of cookies provided by Google.

Like many other websites, [www.metasrc.com](http://www.metasrc.com/) makes use of log files using Google Analytics. These files merely log visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services's analytics. The information inside the log files include anonymized internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, region, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. The IP addresses stored in these log files are anonymized so they are not personally traceable to the user. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather general but not personally identifiable demographic information. This means that the data we store is not personally traceable back to you, and has therefore been rendered anonymous. Google Analytics data will be automatically deleted after a maximum of 26 months.

You may opt out of Google Analytics at any time. One method is to install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on from Google, located here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

Google is committed to protecting the confidentiality and security of Google Analytics data. You may find more information here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

Visit <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites> to learn more about how Google processes data.

THIRD-PARTIES & ADVERTISEMENTS

Third-parties, which include our advertising partners and their ad technology providers, may use third-party cookies and web beacons on our site to deliver targeted advertising and marketing to you.

Our advertising partners include: ZAM, Venatus (EU).

You may learn how our advertising partner(s) use your information at the following URLs:

<https://www.zam.com/legal/privacy>

<https://www.venatusmedia.com/privacy/>

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on [www.metasrc.com](http://www.metasrc.com/) and are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as Cookies, Javascript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

METAsrc has no access to or control over any technologies, including cookies placed on behalf of third-party ad networks, nor do we have access to any data gathered on their behalf. We are not affiliated with these third-parties, and they are governed by their own Privacy Policies. We recommend referring to the Privacy Policy of our advertising partner(s) if you have any concerns over their practices with data and their technology providers.

Personalized Advertisements

You may opt out of receiving personalized advertisements from advertisers or advertising networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or who subscribe to the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out sections on the websites of each of those organizations. You may find those websites here:

Network Advertising Initiative: <https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

Digital Advertising Alliance: <https://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance: <https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>

When you opt out of personalized advertising, you will still continue to receive online advertisements on our site.

PERSONAL DATA – YOUR RIGHTS

If you are located in the European Economic Alliance (“EEA”), you have rights in relation to the Personal Data any business holds about you:

In the case of [www.metasrc.com](http://www.metasrc.com/), we do not hold or process any Personal Data..

However, other businesses, including but not limited to third-party advertising networks and their technology providers, whom we are not affiliated with, may hold certain data that may be personally identifiable to you, including, but not limited to: your internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, region, Internet Service Provider (ISP), and browsing activity. You have the right to contact the Data Protection Officer of these entities to obtain access to any Personal Data they have about you. You also have the right to correct, erase, or object to the processing of any of your Personal Data. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a legal authority regarding the use of your Personal Data.

COOKIE POLICY

When you use the website, we and our third party partners, such as advertising networks, social media widgets, and analytics providers (see below for more details on these partners) may use “cookies” ([What Are Cookies?](https://cookies.insites.com/about-cookies/)) and other similar technologies to collect information about how the website is accessed.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. Deleting or blocking certain cookies may cause the website to not work properly.

The types of cookies you may receive from using our site include:

Strictly Necessary Cookies

These are cookies that are required for the operation of the website. They include, for example: cookies that are required to use the Facebook & Twitter Social Media Widgets on the toolbar and consent compliance cookies.

Performance Cookies

Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track user interactions, as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how users use [www.metasrc.com](http://www.metasrc.com/). This information will be used to compile reports and disclose trends that help us improve the website, without identifying individual visitors. The data gathered from this cookie is anonymous and not personally traceable back to you, because it is set to make your IP address anonymous when it is sent to Google Analytics.

You may opt out of Google Analytics at any time. One method is to install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on from Google, located here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

You can learn more about how Google uses cookies here: <https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies>

Third-Party/Targeting Cookies

You may receive third-party cookies from our advertising partner(s) and their ad technology providers. Third-party advertisers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on [www.metasrc.com](http://www.metasrc.com/) and are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as Cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

When they provide such services, they are governed by their own privacy policies. We do not have access or control to any of the technologies, including cookies, placed by any third-parties.

CONSENT GATHERING

Users in the EEA, or where otherwise legally required by the ePrivacy Directive or GDPR, should be presented with a Cookie Banner upon first load of the site. This banner gathers consent for the use of our performance cookies (Google Analytics) described in our Cookie Policy.

These users should also receive a third-party Consent Management Platform (CMP) banner from our advertising partner which allows the user to control, on a granular level, advertising preferences, including: cookies, personalization, and technology providers relating to the advertisements shown on this site. We do not have access to the preferences you set with this tool and have no way to set them for you. Therefore, your interaction with this tool dictates the types of technologies (cookies, etc.) and advertising you will receive from third-party advertiser(s) while visiting our site.

It is your responsibility to interact with the tool to make your consent known to the advertiser.

We want to make sure your preferences are respected. Contact us at [privacy@metasrc.com](mailto:privacy@metasrc.com) if any of the consent gathering tools are not working properly for you.

CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. [www.metasrc.com](http://www.metasrc.com/) does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that [www.metasrc.com](http://www.metasrc.com/) has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Augus 1st, 2018.

Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
